(Penny:)Sheldon, sweetie, shut up.
(Bernadette:)One of the things that helped me get through
Howard being in space for so long...
(Bernadette:)...was getting married before he left.
(Penny:)Bernadette, sweetie, shut up.
(Raj:)Okay, I have a request to make.
(Amy:)And now he can talk.
(Amy:)I want to cut open your brain
and see what the heck's going on in there.
(Raj:)The only person allowed
inside this head is Dr. Phil.
Anyway, I spoke to my new lady friend
about meeting you all.
(Raj:)She thought it would be easier
for her to start with just one.
(Sheldon:)Gee, I don't know,
my schedule is a little busy.
(Raj:)Actually, I was thinking Leonard.
Well, thank you, Raj, I'd be honored.
(Howard:)What the hell?
I thought I was your best friend.
(Raj:)You are, but you've got
kind of a big personality...
(Raj:)...with your flashy clothes
and your Woody Allen swagger.